I Am Chris Farley is a documentary film directed by Brent Hodge.
I am Chris Farley tells his hilarious, touching and wildly entertaining story - from his early days in Madison, Wisconsin, to his time at
Second City and Saturday Night Live, then finally his film career (which included hits like Tommy Boy and Black Sheep).
The film showcases his most memorable characters and skits from film and television and also includes interviews and insights from his co-stars,
family and friends - including the likes of Christina Applegate, Dan Aykroyd, Mike Myers, Bob Odenkirk, Bob Saget and Adam Sandler.
Self (archive footage), played by Chris Farley.
Self, played by Christina Applegate.
Self, played by Tom Arnold.
Self, played by Dan Aykroyd.
Self, played by Lorri Bagley.
Self, played by Bo Derek.
I Am Chris Farley is a 2015 documentary film based on the life of comedian and actor Chris Farley, co-directed by
Brent Hodge of Hodgee Films and Derik Murray, who was also a producer, of Network Entertainment.
The production features interviews with numerous actors, comedians
and others who worked with Farley during his career.
The film explores themes of comedian, biography, hollywood.
The tone is emotional.